Guide to the James H. Karales photographs, 1953-2006 and undated RL.10017
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961, 2 boxes
  - SNCC Finished Prints
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-087)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2714
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-088)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2715
      Same content as print RL-10017-P097 (16 x 20 inches).
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-089)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2716
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-090)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2717
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-091)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2718
      Same content as print RL-10017-P103 (16 x 20 inches).
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-092)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2719
      Same content as RL-10017-P095 (16 x 20 inches).
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-093)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2720
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-094)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2721
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-095)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2751
      Same content as print RL-10017-P092 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-096)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2752
      Same content as print RL-10017-P084 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-097)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2753
      Same content as print RL-10017-P088 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-098)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2754
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-099)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2774
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-100)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2775
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-101)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2776
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-102)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2777
      Same content as RL-10017-P085 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC), 1960-1961; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-103)
      Legacy identifiers: GDC 2783
      Same content as RL-10017-P091 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
- Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962, 4 boxes
  Taken by Karales as he traveled with King and his entourage to marches and speeches in various locations, the images depict King, his family, and civil rights movement participants, including Rosa Parks. One series of images feature King at home with Coretta Scott King and his children and convey a sense of casual intimacy. Images taken during civil rights protests capture King interacting with participants, and King and other individuals speaking at rallies and in churches.
  Series includes large black-and-white gelatin silver prints ranging in size from as well as contact sheets and work prints (5x7 and 8x10 inches); there are no negatives. Other civil rights movement materials are housed in the Civil Rights Series and the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) Series. These images were published in Look magazine. All prints are marked on back with the photographer's roll and frame number.
  - MLK Jr. Contact Sheets, 3 folders; 19 prints
    The contact sheets bear Karales' markings, indicating images selected for proof prints or finished prints. Folders in boxes are marked with roll numbers.
    - Contact sheets: Job 1028, rolls 1-6; 8-16; 18-19; 21-22; and 24-26 (Box 9)
  - MLK Jr. Work Prints, 5x7 and 8x10, 30 folders; 87 prints
    Contains 30 5x7 and 57 8x10 work prints. Numbers represent rolls and frames, and are marked on the backs of the prints. Folders in boxes are titled with the roll numbers housed within. There are 2 folders of duplicate sheets, one for each size.
    - Work prints, 5x7 and 8x10: Job 1028 roll numbers 1, 3-5, 7-22, 24-25, and 27-29, and duplicates (Box 9)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Finished Prints, 14 prints
    Thirteen 11x14 inch and one 16x20 inch black-and-white gelatin silver prints, selected from several hundred frames taken by Karales while he traveled with King's entourage in Georgia and Alabama.
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-104)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 1:15; GDC 2558
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-105)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 3:5; GDC 2541
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-106)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 3:17; GDC 2649
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-107)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 4:5; GDC 2578
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-108)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 4:11; F-KAR.P08
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-109)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 7:22; GDC 2557
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-110)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 7:27; GDC 2556
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-111)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 7:28; GDC 2559
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 25, Image RL-10017-P-112)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 7:32; GDC 2664
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-113)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 11:18; GDC 2555
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-114)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 11:26; GDC 2640
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-115)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 13:15; GDC 2676
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-116)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 20:33; F-KAR.P09
      Print slightly creased on bottom corner, small stains on bottom edge.
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-117)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 21:6; GDC 2648
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-118)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 21:17; GDC 2631
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-119)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 25:36; GDC 2574
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-120)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 26:11; GDC 2543
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-121)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 29:32; GDC 2633
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1962; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 27, Image RL-10017-P-122)
      Legacy identifiers: 1028 20:17
- Vietnam War, 1963-1967, 14 boxes
  On assignment with Look magazine from 1963 to 1967, Karales travelled to South Vietnam twice to cover U.S. Special Forces units and their role during the Vietnam War. Selected images from the thousands of frames shot by Karales were published in Look magazine, and were reproduced extensively for other publications. All of the prints are in black-and-white, but there is a large group of over 1100 color slides. There are also contact sheets and small work prints included in this series. A CD-R with 31 jpeg files of black-and-white Vietnam images taken by Karales is included; the files have been migrated to a library server.
  Subjects in the images include: U.S. soldiers in Saigon, in combat, and at rest; daily interactions between American soldiers and Vietnamese civilians, including soldiers giving away candy, food, medical supplies, and other items; images of dead U.S. and Viet Cong; village scenes, including attacks on villages and subsequent relocation efforts; a Catholic chaplain's service; Vietnamese prison camps and hospitals; U.S. doctors in Vietnam; a Montagnard refugee camp; patrol scenes and other action in the field and on rivers; a delta rice and sugar cane factories, with workers in some images; schools and temples; and Saigon street scenes, often with U.S. soldiers buying goods or interacting with civilians. Some images are aerial shots. There are images of prominent figures such as Sam Castan (reporter for Look, who worked closely with Karales and died in Vietnam), D. Halberstam, Ray Hernandon, and General Westmoreland. There are also a few pictures of Karales.
  Some images bear titles assigned by Karales; titles in brackets supplied by library staff. Prints are often stamped on the back with a year. All prints are marked on back with the roll and frame number. NOTE: titles on archival folders were taken from original envelopes, but often refer only to a subset of images in that folder; for example, a folder marked "Construction" may in fact contain only five or six images of construction projects, with the rest being street and combat scenes.
  - Vietnam Contact Sheets, 35 folders; 250 prints
    The 250 contact sheets include Karales' markings indicating images selected for proof prints or finished prints. In some cases there are individual frames cut from the original contact sheets. There do not appear to be duplicate sheets. Folders in boxes are marked with roll numbers.
    - Contact sheets: Job 1610, rolls 1-192 (with some gaps in roll numbers) and an unidentified roll; 1610 test roll; Job 2226, rolls 1-9; Job 2735, rolls 1-17; and prints marked B34870, B34856, B37929, and B37930 (Box 10)
  - Vietnam Work Prints, 8x10, 95 folders; 214 prints
    - Work prints, 8x10: Job 1610, roll numbers 3-192 (with gaps in roll numbers); Job 2226, rolls 1 and 3; Job 2735, rolls 2-4, 10, and an unidentified roll (Box 11-13)
  - Vietnam Color Slides, 35 folders; 1188 slides
    Original titles found on slide boxes and packets are retained on folders. Titles often refer to only a few of the images contained in the group of slides; other subjects are usually also present.
    - unspecified, slides (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Buddhist temple, 4 slides (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Feb. 65, 14 slides (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 65 Feb. 26, 80 slides (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 65 Feb. 26, 66 slides (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 65 Feb. 26, 80 slides (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 65 Mar. 2, 80 slides (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 65 Mar. 2, 75 slides (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Helicopters and wounded, 75 slides (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - U.S. dead (seems to only have one related shot, a casket in a hearse), 20 slides (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - American funeral, 21 slides (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Westmorland, 49 slides (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Vietnam 1964, 88 slides (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Buddhist demonstration, 114 slides (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Wounded, 29 slides (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Helicopters, 3 slides (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Hass Fuch dead, 34 slides (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - G.I., 34 slides (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - [Untitled], 1 slide (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Communism, 26 slides (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Construction, 26 slides (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - War '66, 27 slides (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Vietnamese scenes, 34 slides (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Vietnam street scenes, 16 slides (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bar in Saigon, 24 slides (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Goods on street - Saigon, 17 slides (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Flea market, 32 slides (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Execution wall - main market, 30 slides (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Ship workers -Saigon, 15 slides (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Days in the trees [Various shots of people on the street and at work sites, almost all wearing hats], 11 slides (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Rejects, 192 slides (Box 14, Folder 16)
      The majority depict street scenes and construction sites, with about two dozen images taken at a military base and airport.
    - Field scenes, 32 slides (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - G.I. in Saigon, 14 slides (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam Negatives, 233 negative folders
    Approximately negative strips in several hundred folders, representing thousands of images for Jobs 1610, 2226, and others. Some are large-format, but most are 35mm strips, approximately 5 to a folder (segregated by roll). Roll numbers are marked on the negative folders.
    - Negatives: Jobs 1610, rolls 1-192 and a test roll; 2226 1-9; 2226 with "B" roll codes; and 2735 with "B" codes (Box 15-18)
  - Vietnam Finished Prints
    Fourteen black-and-white gelatin silver prints selected from the thousands of images Karales took in during two trips to combat areas in Vietnam in the 1960s. A large series of color slides are also found in this series.
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-123)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 40:25; GDC 2568
      Same content as RL-10017-P129 (16 x 20 inches).
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-124)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 48:30; GDC 2569
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-125)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 49:21; GDC 2606
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-126)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 104:15; GDC 2607
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-127)
      Legacy identifiers: B34856:19; GDC 2651
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-128)
      Legacy identifiers: B37930: 21
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-129)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 40:25
      Same content as print RL-10017-P123 (11 x 14 inches); mounted.
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-130)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 43:30
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-131)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 45:31
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-132)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 48:12
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-133)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 120:26; GDC 2600
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; 20 x24 inches) (Box 29, Image RL-10017-P-134)
      Legacy identifiers: 2735 11:10A
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; 8.5 x 13.5 in (Box 29, Image RL-10017-P-135)
      Legacy identifiers: 1610 40:23; GDC 2773
    - Vietnam, 1963-1967; (9 x 13.5 inches) (Box 29, Image RL-10017-P-136)
      Legacy identifiers: 47:12; GDC 2780
- Civil Rights Movement, 1965, 5 boxes
  These images taken by Karales during the march for voting rights from Selma to Montgomery, Alabama, March 1965, while on assignment for Look magazine. Includes the widely-reproduced photographs of an African American boy enveloped by the U.S. flag, and civil rights marchers with the U.S. flag on the crest of a hill. The following civil rights movement leaders and activists are also depicted: Andrew Young (2309:31, 38, 41, 44), Martin Luther King, Jr. (2309:33, 37, 40, 44), James Baldwin, the author of Selma to Montgomery, Alabama Civil Rights March (2039:44), Rabbi Abraham Joshua Heschel (2309:14, 37), whose papers are also held by the Rubenstein Library, and Joan Baez (2039:44).
  Series includes 13 large black-and-white gelatin silver prints ranging in size from 11x14 to 20x24 inches, as well as contact sheets and work prints (5x7 and 8x10 inches), and negatives. Related civil rights movement images are housed in the Martin Luther King Jr. Series and the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) Series. All prints are marked on the back with the photographer's roll and frame number.
  - Civil Rights Contact Sheets, 5 folders, 56 prints
    The contact sheets include Karales' markings indicating images selected for proof prints or finished prints. The job number represented is 2309, all rolls. There do not seem to be duplicate sheets.
    - Contact sheets: Job 2309 (Box 19)
  - Civil Rights Work Prints, 59 folders; 128 prints
    Contains 57 5x7 and 71 8x10 work prints. Numbers represent rolls and frames, and are marked on the backs of the prints. Folders are titled with the roll numbers housed within. Typically only a few frames were developed from each roll, with the exception of rolls 33-44, for which at least half a dozen frames were printed. Two folders house 14 duplicate prints.
    - Work prints: Job 2309, roll numbers 1-44, with a few gaps in roll numbers (Box 19)
  - Civil Rights Negatives Series, 50 negative folders
    Approximately 250 negative strips accompanied by a few large-format negatives, representing film rolls 1 through 50 of Job 2309. Negative folders are labeled with roll numbers.
    - Negatives: Job 2309, rolls 1-50 (Box 20)
  - Civil Rights Finished Prints, 8 folders, 13 prints
    Four black-and-white silver gelatin prints measuring 11x14 inches, eight measuring 16x20 inches, and one 20x24 print. Several prints share similar content. Some are matted. Where possible, the prints are arranged chronologically by the original job, roll and frame numbers. If no roll and frame numbers exist, the prints are arranged by the Gary Davis Collection (GDC) number. Some images bear original titles; titles in brackets have been supplied by library staff.
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-137)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 4:32
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-138)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 7:14; GDC 2729
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-139)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 15:8; GDC 2628
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-140)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 17:12A; GDC 2560
      Same content as RL-10017-P145 (16 x 20 inches).
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-141)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 4:19
      Matted.
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-142)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 7:30
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (10.75 x 16.5 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-143)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 8: 27. Matted.
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (10.625 x 16.25 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-216)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 8:27.
      Same content as print RL-10017-P143 (10.75 x 16.5 inches); digital print by Alex Harris, 2005; matted.
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-144)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 13:22; GDC 2309?
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-145)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 17:12A; GDC 2309?
      Same content as print RL-10017-P140; mounted.
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-146)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 20:18; GDC 2785
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-147)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 40:24; GDC 2309?
    - Selma to Montgomery March, Alabama, 1965; (20 x 24 inches) (Box 29, Image RL-10017-P-148)
      Legacy identifiers: 2309 1:31A
- Lower East Side (N.Y), 1969, 1975, 1985, 6 boxes
  Series comprises black-and-white images taken by Karales during three visits roughly ten years apart to New York City's Lower East Side neighborhoods, as part of an assignment with Look magazine. They feature street scenes and individual portraits of East Side families, children, and other individuals in settings such as neighborhood games, a community clean-up of derelict building lots, and other social gatherings. The Reverend Bruce Ritter, the founder of the Covenant House homeless youth shelter, is featured in many portraits and scenes. A transcript of a lengthy interview with Father Ritter is also found in the Lower East Side Subseries of the Manuscripts and Printed Materials Series.
  Series includes 17 large black-and-white gelatin silver prints, measuring 11x14 inches, as well as contact sheets, work prints (5x7 and 8x10 inches), and negatives. With a few exceptions, the large prints do not indicate the date they were taken.
  - Lower East Side Contact Sheets, 15 folders, 172 prints
    Jobs represented: Job 74, 2175, 5264, and F740. It is not clear which of the jobs pertain to which travel dates.
    - Contact sheets: Job 74, rolls 1-19 (for which there do not appear to be prints); Job 2175, rolls 1-12; Job 5264, rolls 1-67, 74-84; and Job F740, rolls 1-26 (Box 21)
  - Lower East Side Work Prints, 34 folders; 175 prints
    Contains 2 4x6, 47 5x7, and 126 8x10 work prints. Numbers represent rolls and frames, and are marked on the backs of the prints. Of the 47 5x7 prints, 5 are duplicates; of the 126 5x7 prints, 39 are duplicates. Jobs represented are: 2175, 1075 (for which there are no contact sheets), 5264, and F740. Folders are titled with the roll numbers housed within.
    - Work prints: Job 2175, rolls 1-11; Job 5264, rolls 6-83, with some gaps in numbers; and Job 1075, rolls 10-12; and duplicates (Box 21-22)
  - Lower East Side Negatives, 50 negative folders
    - Negatives: roll numbers 1-40 and 1A-10A (Box 23)
  - Lower East Side Finished Prints, 17 prints
    Scope and Contents
    These seventeen gelatin silver prints range in size from 11x14 inches to 16x20 inches, and were selected by Karales from his Lower East Side images shot in 1969, 1975, and 1985. With only two exceptions, the images do not indicate the date they were taken and are arranged in order as received. Titles in brackets were supplied by library staff.
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-149)
      Legacy identifiers: 5264 15:34; GDC 2737
      Same content as print RL-10017-P158 (16 x 20 inches).
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-150)
      Legacy identifiers: 5264 16:7; GDC 2726
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-151)
      Legacy identifiers: 5264 22:2; GDC 2723
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-152)
      Legacy identifiers: 5264 31:15; GDC 2739
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-153)
      Legacy identifiers: 5264 45:20A; GDC 2735
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-154)
      Legacy identifiers: 74 4:32; GDC 2740
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-155)
      Legacy identifiers: 74 4:35; GDC 2736
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (11 x 14 inches) (Box 26, Image RL-10017-P-156)
      Legacy identifiers: 74 12:12; GDC 2738
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; 14 x 17 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-157)
      Legacy identifiers: 5264 17:12; GDC 2788
    - Lower East Side, New York, 1969; (16 x 20 inches) (Box 28, Image RL-10017-P-158)
      Legacy identifiers: 5264 15:34; GDC 2787